[{"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "I mean, historically, since the Second World War, say, is there evidence to say that when you go really negative against a vulnerable opponent perhaps, you'll win?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "It's tamed and it's a mediocre as a piece of advertising.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "I mean -- I don't think the gloves have come off here, have they?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Which is probably the sign of a good one, right?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well -- I guess that's one hot issue, but I would say there's something even more -- which is people don't really know who Romney is.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Would you go there if you were Obama?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "My guess is that Rubio indeed will not be the vice presidential nominee.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "What do you make of it or what's going on behind the scenes here?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "ICH: I don't think there really is a smart pick.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Who's the smart pick?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Probably, but I have a feeling in this case it's pretty small potatoes.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Am I right to be that cynical?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, this is an historical battle within the Constitution going back to Andrew Jackson who defied Congress and said you pass the law, now you execute it.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "How justified is the criticism?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "So the constitutional principle versus the political reality.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Why wouldn't they just be coming out with it otherwise?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I think that the House will not vote contempt.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "What do you think will happen?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "To be fair to Frank, I don't think he likes the negative ads.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Michael Steele, former chairman of the RNC, Republican National Committee, criticizes Mitt Romney for taking a Barack Obama statement that he doesn't know anything about the economy when he was referring to John McCain taking it out of context and then Mitt Romney says well, if it was out of context, what's sauce for the goose?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, it isn't necessarily -- the answer is yes, but contrasting, I think, Barack Obama's ideas are better than Mitt Romney's.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Can a presidential candidate win through positivity alone?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, first let me say, I have to be very limited in what I can say to you about this, Piers.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "All of these skills are pretty seriously tested in this case because eon the face of it it's pretty grim for Penn State, isn't it?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Look, just to be clear, to protect myself, I didn't know we would be talking about this subject tonight.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Is that the problem for Penn State, that when you have such an iconic character, with Joe Paterno, for example, wielding such power through his just years of experience, decades of experience, that if it turns out that Sandusky is guilty and gets wayed (ph) off for a long time and it's sort of confirmed again that Joe Paterno knew and others knew, that that brings shame to Penn State, doesn't it, just an institution, that more young boys were allowed to be abused simply because those in positions of authority, for whatever reason, didn't do anything?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, without focusing on just higher education, I think a good part of government's problem is an absence of transparency.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Do you think there's been a seismic shock to the whole system in this country?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "It's -- they Google.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What is the kind of interview that absolutely sends you demented?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "You're starting right off there.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What do you think of America right now?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "That's a really good question.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "How much has that guided your sense of people not being reliant on their parents?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Are you an Obama man at heart?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Moral compass.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What is the kind of leader that you're craving in an American president?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "More than one and less than five.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Do you want to name how many you've rolled in the hay with?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "She actually has a hay bale in her bedroom.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Did you actually roll in the hay with her?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I have no problem with that.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Why shouldn't their opinion, their Tweets be as valuable to the world as yours or mine?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "What's interesting about it in my life is I made some great albums in the '90s and -- which become sort of almost like a mill stone around my neck.", "docId": "120620pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "What do you feel about this album?", "qSentId": 572}]